♪ ♪
Mr. Barnett, you
stated that you left work
at the Bedford Country
Club after 1:00 a.m.
Did you see anything in
the country club parking lot?
Well, as I was
walking to my car,
I saw Mr. Walsh's car.
It looked like there
was some difficulty,
so I went over.
He was lying on the ground,
bleeding from his head.
He needed help.
I knew there was a
phone at the guard gate.
But then I spotted another car
and it looked like there
was someone inside,
so I ran to it.
It was Drew Carey.
Drew Carey the defendant?
Yes. He seemed to be passed out.
And there was a
lug wrench in his lap.
It was covered with blood.
Mr. Walsh and Mr. Carey
had argued violently earlier,
but I never thought
Mr. Carey would murder him.
Objection.
This witness's thoughts
are irrelevant,
unfounded and conjecture.
I didn't kill Uncle Edwin!
Mr. Carey. Sit down, Drew.
I didn't kill him,
but I know who did.
If someone would
put up my bail, I...
Mr. Matlock,
control your client.
Yes, ma'am.
I swear to you, I'll
tape your mouth shut.
Sorry, Your Honor.
This fight you mentioned,
Mr. Barnett, did
you actually see it
or did you just hear about it?
Happened right in front of me.
Mr. Walsh, Drew's uncle,
was sitting at the
bar with Mr. Horton.
He's the chief executive
officer of Horton Aviation
where Mr. Walsh worked.
Ed, please.
Ah, thank you.
We've had this
conversation before.
I don't want to have it again.
But this is trouble,
Jonathan, big trouble.
For you, for me,
for the company.
Edwin, you worry too much.
I'd like to go home
now. I'm exhausted.
Well go ahead. I
can't go just now.
You're not coming?
I'm auditing the club books.
I'll be home after 1:00.
I won't wait up.
Oh, hey, hey, Valerie.
Where's your fiancée?
Out looking for a rich husband.
Aw, she broke your engagement?
Couldn't happen
to a nicer guy, right?
Hey, Martin.
Double tequila straight up.
How you doing, Uncle Edwin?
I've been looking for you.
Don't serve him, Martin.
Don't serve me?
It's time you stopped
feeling so sorry for yourself.
Uncle Edwin, I
don't want a pep talk.
I just lost Caroline,
my money...
Nobody stole the money from you.
You blew it.
$2 million, your
entire inheritance
on some fly-by-night
software company.
I-I don't need a lecture.
I need a loan.
I've offered you a job, Drew.
A lousy entry-level
job at a lousy salary.
I started that way.
So did your father.
Look, you can loan me the money.
You know you can.
I won't do it.
Don't ask me again.
If I had half, you
know, maybe Caroline...
She's a cash register.
Good riddance.
Good riddance?!
You're making
a fool of yourself.
You're a big man, Uncle Edwin.
But just wait.
Everybody falls.
I did, and you will, too!
Then Drew stormed out.
So Mr. Carey
threatened his uncle?
Your Honor, that doesn't
sound like a threat to me.
I just told him
off! I was upset!
Mr. Carey, you are out of order.
- I never said...
Drew, sit down!
I'm sorry, Your Honor.
I didn't kill him!
Your Honor, may I have
a moment with my client?
- Explain gag.
Explain restraint.
This court is in
recess for 15 minutes.
What the hell's the
matter with you?!
They're burying me and
you're just sitting there!
How many times have you
ever been in a courtroom?
Twice.
I've spent more
years in a courtroom
than you've been alive.
I've listened in courtrooms,
I've spoken in courtrooms,
I've won in courtrooms.
But there's one thing I've
never done in a courtroom,
and that's just sit there.
Okay.
Hey, but we both know
Valerie killed Uncle Edwin.
She'll be on the stand next.
Yeah, but she'll lie. We'll see.
But... No buts,
no ifs, no ands, no
maybes. You got that?
You were a nice kid.
Good-natured, responsible.
How did you turn
out to be such a jerk?
Drew did nothing
but argue with Edwin.
So the argument they
had that night at the club
wasn't their first?
No.
Drew wanted a loan.
He wanted one for a long time.
Edwin refused, of course,
and then Drew gave him no peace.
He followed him everywhere.
He confronted him.
He blamed him. Don't
even think about it.
For what, I don't know.
Were these
arguments ever violent?
They came close.
Edwin was losing patience.
He referred to
their confrontations
as "Drew's temper tantrums."
That's a lie! Hey.
Whatever our differences,
he respected me.
He offered me a job that night.
You think I'd kill somebody
that offered me a job?
Young man, sit down.
I can't take this anymore.
No, I can't handle this.
Bailiff, stop him.
You got to go back to your seat.
Hey, hey, come back here!
Looks as though
we will be adding
escape and battery
on a peace officer
to the charges against
your client, Mr. Matlock.
This court is now in recess.
You go that way.
Hey, stop! Carey!
Carey, stop! Stop!
Hey, sorry, it won't start.
You couldn't call?
Les, I've had a
very difficult day.
You could have called.
Les, I said you could eat here
while they're working
on your kitchen.
Nobody said anything
about cooking for me.
You could have called.
It's, it's not like we're
married or anything.
We're not even going together.
Heaven forbid.
But you could have called.
Les, I've had a
very difficult day.
Yeah, I know, I heard
about it on the radio.
Desperate criminal
escapes courthouse.
Boy, you pick some
real winners, don't you?
He didn't do it.
Of course he did.
No, he didn't.
Then why else would he run away?
Because he doesn't have
the sense God gave a goldfish.
Oh, dumb, too, huh?
Les, if your mother
left you $2 million,
would you grow up to be a jerk?
She did, and I'm
a lovely person.
What is this?
Ham hocks and beans.
Where'd you get the ham hocks?
What do you mean,
where'd I get the ham hocks?
Out of your refrigerator.
There were no ham
hocks in the refrigerator.
Well... I guess I'll go
see if I can find him.
Where're you going?
See if I can find him. I...
Oh, aren't you gonna eat first?
I don't want any.
You don't want any?!
I've been cooking all day!
You can at least
try a bite or two.
You're hot stuff, you know that?
I mean, I've been
cooking all day!
I missed Oprah, Phil Donahue,
Joan Rivers and Dr. Ruth.
I don't know what's going on!
Hey, you could've called!
You killed him, Valerie.
Get out of my house.
Not until you tell
me you killed him.
I didn't kill Edwin;
he was my husband.
What about the Riverview Motel?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
And that guy you
were with... Aunt Val.
Does he know how much
you loved Uncle Edwin?
I saw you with him.
In a restaurant.
I followed you, Aunt Val.
You little creep.
Uncle Edwin found out
about your affair, didn't he?
And then he threatened
to divorce you.
You don't want that.
Your boyfriend, he's got
muscles but he hasn't got dough.
I didn't kill Edwin. Now leave!
You didn't go home the night
Uncle Edwin was murdered.
You waited outside the club
and hit him on the head
with his own wrench!
No!
All right, I didn't come home.
I was at the Riverview Motel.
Hello? Anybody home?
In here!
Oh, it figures.
Let go of her.
This is Valerie Walsh
at 1245 Sky Way.
Please send the
police immediate...
Drew!
Give her back her keys and
sit down and wait for the police.
What are you, nuts?
Hey!
Drew!
You see where he was headed?
No.
Any idea where he was headed?
Uh, no.
O-Officer, I'm his lawyer.
Mr. Matlock, are
you gonna stick to
this client-lawyer privileged
information business?
This man could be a murderer.
Oh, I don't think so.
He-he's pretty
much of a jackass,
but I don't think
he'd kill anybody.
Thanks for your
help. Yeah, right.
Uh, Mrs. Walsh...
I have a lover; his
name is Mark Tannen.
At the time of the murder, we
were at the Riverview Motel.
Boy, you come right
out with it, don't you?
Uh, wh-why didn't, uh,
you mention your lover
the first time we met?
My affair has nothing to
do with Edwin's murder.
Mark is a good man and
he loves me and I love him.
Uh, is... got a phone
number on-on hand?
555-9737.
But he's out of town.
Uh, uh, uh... seven.
Uh, did, uh, did-did Mr. Horton
and your husband, uh, get along?
I mean, were they, were
they friends, business friends?
They argued.
They did?
Constantly.
Here, at the club...
Club? That night?
About what?
Well, I couldn't really
hear them, but I know
they were definitely arguing.
And here?
Behind closed doors.
Probably something having
to do with Horton Aviation.
Edwin was president
and Jonathan was CEO.
Edwin kept his business from me.
Of course, you kept
certain things from him.
That's not funny.
Um, wh-why didn't you mention
th-their arguments before?
I thought that
Drew had killed him.
Oh, you thought Drew...
Mm.
And, uh, nobody had accused you.
That, too.
Good-bye, Mr. Matlock.
Oh, uh...
We're tied four to four
in the seventh inning.
We have runners at first
and second with only one out.
And Al Warner with that 95
mile-an-hour fastball of his
is challenging McCord.
Excuse me.
35 for a double, 40 for cable.
List of movies is over there.
Yeah, well...
uh, what I really want
is a list of people
that stayed here
on the night of September 12.
You got to be a cop and
you got to have a warrant.
Oh.
Oh, darn, you know,
all I've got is one of these.
Actually, I've got two.
Hey, rather than ruin it,
why don't I just
take the whole thing.
Okay.
Mr. Matlock, if I don't get
to the airport in 15 minutes,
I'm gonna miss my
plane for Washington,
and that means I'll miss my
appointment at the Pentagon.
Uh, what,
what were you and Edwin
Walsh arguing about that night?
Who said we were arguing?
Valerie Walsh.
What the hell does she know?
No, Edwin and I
were just talking.
About what?
Can't say.
Why not?
We work with the
Defense Department.
Oh, classified.
That's right, that's right.
Does that answer your
question, Mr. Matlock?
Oh, of course, of course.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I've got to make a
phone call. Yes, sir.
Mr. Walsh's office
is-is on this floor?
Two doors down to the right.
Oh, thank you.
Well, where'd everything go?
Storage mostly.
They cleaned this room
out the day after the murder.
Not that there was ever
much in here to begin with.
Mr. Walsh didn't
believe in frills.
He spent company money like
it came out of his own pocket.
Well, is it standard
procedure around here
to put a person's
stuff in storage
before his body even gets cold?
All I know is, Mr. Horton
gave the order.
And when he says "jump,"
we don't ask why, we just...
Say, "How high?"
Yep. Oh, yeah.
Mark, it's ready.
All right.
Mark Tannen, right?
Drew Carey.
Valerie's nephew.
I don't know any Valerie.
And get off my truck.
Hey, look, look!
Buddy, I know all
about you and Aunt Val,
so you can cooperate or
the police will know, too.
What do you want?
Where were you the night
her husband was murdered?
I was with her.
Yeah, uh, where?
Riverview Motel.
Oh, then how come your name
wasn't in the motel registry?
Says who?
Well, I have it right here.
And you know damn
well your name isn't in it.
Now, come on, Mark.
Did she murder Edwin or did you?
Ow!
Who are you?
Where'd you come from?
You're the killer!
Uh, Ben's not here!
I'll wait.
Uh, he-he went to Buffalo
to a lawyers convention.
He won't be back for weeks.
Uh, this is not a good hideout.
Yeah, uh, policemen
are in and out of here
all the time, you know.
Policemen just love Ben.
And Ben's friends.
Th-They drop in
every ten seconds or so
to see me and just
to see how I'm doing.
One's due here any second now.
Would you just stop talking
for a minute there, fella?
Ben!
Ixnay, the killernay.
What?
Oh, hi, Ben. Look...
Call the police!
You can't do that!
Don't-don't give me
that-that lawyer-client
relationship garbage!
I'm off the case!
Give me the keys. You can't!
Mark Tannen's the killer.
I saw him today. No, no.
He lied to me. I'm going
back there tomorrow.
Give me the keys to the car.
I have to find out who
killed Uncle Edwin!
No! Give me the keys!
You've made me look like
the worst kind of stupid lawyer
who can't even
control his own client.
You're spoiled, you're
arrogant, you're stupid.
Give me the keys!
Ben, let me explain...
Shut up and sit down!
Now, listen, Ben...
Ben said sit down!
You're wearing my best suit!
Well, your friend
threw flour on mine,
and this is all I could find.
Be careful with it.
I see you cleaned
up the kitchen.
Yeah, I-I can't eat breakfast
in the middle of a mess.
You didn't get anything on...
No, no, no, no.
Here, know what, just sit
down and-and eat, okay?
Eat.
Oh! Yeah.
Breakfast.
Oh, boy!
I love... breakfast.
Yeah. Mmm! Mm-mm-mm-mm-mm-mm!
Mmm...
A little something to get
you started with. Yeah.
Mmm...
Yeah.
I'm glad you got done
before Les gets over here.
Who is he? Neighbor.
Retired, plastics.
When something
breaks down in his house,
he hangs around over here.
Weird dude.
Yeah.
'Course I'm a little weird
myself, too, sometimes,
so we make a pretty good team.
Drew...
I've been thinking about you.
You've been unhappy for
a long time, haven't you?
I... I can understand now.
I mean, you're...
wanted for murder,
and your mother
left you $2 million,
and you blew that.
And in one roll of
the dice... Gone.
Somewhere up there, uh...
my father's laughing at me,
saying, "Drew, you're no good.
Never were."
Well, your father
was a hard man.
Hard on himself,
hard on your mother.
He... he tolerated me
'cause I was his lawyer.
He was real hard on you.
My father didn't like me.
Well, your father
didn't like anybody.
But you were his son, so...
Well, I... I liked you.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, you were...
you were a good kid.
You got good marks in school,
and you had a nice personality
and I... I just liked you.
I'll go see who it is.
Stay right here.
Stay out of sight.
Why, Mr. Horton,
what a surprise.
Well, my plane just
got in from Washington,
and, uh, I took the
liberty of dropping by.
Hope you don't mind.
How come?
Well, I was under
the gun yesterday,
and I was rather short with
you; that was rude of me and I...
I want to apologize.
Oh, there's no
apologies necessary.
Classified information
is classified information.
Well, it's no longer classified.
You see, Horton Aviation
is building a new
military supply transport.
And it's going to be
unveiled in about two weeks,
so it's no longer top secret.
And now you know
the... the subject
of my discussion with Edwin.
Oh, that's what you and
Edwin were arguing about...
The military supply
transport. All right.
Argument is, well...
rather a strong word.
We were discussing
design details.
You know, the cant of the
wing, sectors of the hull.
There are thousands
of those details.
It's all very complicated,
but you get the idea?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. And it was, it was
nice of you to-to stop by.
Oh, look at that car.
Now, that's some car!
Well...
Does the leather still
have that leather smell?
Mmm! Well, some of these days.
Uh, Edwin drove a car
a lot like this, didn't he?
Exactly the same. Oh.
All of my executives drive them.
We get the fleet price. Oh.
Oh. You get many flats?
Never.
Never had one.
Well, I guess Edwin
was just unlucky
all the way around that night.
If he had called someone
to change that flat,
he'd probably be alive today.
But that's Edwin.
Counting pennies till the end.
Getting along without him
is going to be just
about impossible. Well...
thanks. See you someday.
Okay.
Mmm...
Well, take care.
Drew, I told you to stay put.
What if he had seen you?
I'd have taken off.
Sooner or later,
you're going to have
to give yourself up to the cops.
You keep taking off, you're
going to wind up dead.
Yeah. I got to get back
to that construction site.
No, no, no, no.
I'll go see what I can unravel.
Oh, but if you
just let me help...
No! We're both in
over our heads already.
Here. Put this on.
Oh, but I can't...
Take off my good suit,
put that on, and stay here.
Ben, I couldn't
sleep last night,
thinking of you alone
here with that killer.
You're wearing Ben's best suit.
You got a car?
Sure. It's parked
in my driveway.
Hey, Ben. Uh...
Looking for your client?
I don't know, Bob. Want one?
He actually decked
the bailiff, huh?
That's the rumor.
Any clues on him?
Nah, not a peep.
I'll bet you could
give us a hand.
Yeah. He's out at my house.
Why don't you take a look?
So, what is it with you
and this kid, huh, Ben?
Why don't you drop him?
Can't do that.
I'm sure the court
will let you withdraw.
Well, more than that.
I know that when you
look at Drew Carey,
you're looking at a jerk.
Well, you are, too.
Well, yeah.
But I knew him when
he was a little kid.
You know? He used to
deliver papers and work.
He was a nice,
honorable little fella.
I know what happened to him.
I know what happened to him,
and I... I guess
that's the difference.
And, uh, besides that,
I don't think he did it.
It's a good case.
Yours? No. I don't think so.
Um, I got to go in and
see Judge Cooksey.
He gets mad when anybody
comes in his office eating,
so...
Uh, Ben, you hear from
that boy, you let us know.
Not a chance!
Look, Mr. Matlock,
I registered under a false name.
That's why it's not there.
What name did you use?
You weren't at the
motel, were you?
Why would I lie?
Well, that's for you to tell me.
Or the police.
And, uh, if I were you,
I'd tell me because
the police a lot of times
don't believe ex-cons.
Do you know?
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
I was at a racetrack outside
of Butler Township in Alabama.
By yourself?
A bunch of guys.
Just so you know,
Valerie told me to lie.
Valerie told you to say
you were at that motel?
She called me
yesterday after that run-in
with you and her nephew.
She doesn't know
where I was that night.
You see, we, um...
had some girls with us.
Mostly for luck. Mr. Matlock?
That night was the only
time I ever broke parole.
Are you going to say anything?
Not unless I have to.
Thanks.
You know what this
means now, don't you?
Hey, what the hell?!
Damn it, Drew.
Now you've stolen Les's car.
Somebody get him!
I'm tired of dealing with you!
Hello?
Ms. Walsh? Uh,
this is Ben Matlock,
Drew Carey's lawyer.
Yes?
I-I only have a
minute to talk to you.
Uh, Drew didn't
kill your husband.
I-I-I don't, I don't
know who did,
but I think we can end
one of our more
immediate problems.
Uh, Drew is on his
way over to see you.
He is? I'm calling the police.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's right.
Call the cops.
Valerie, open up!
Valerie.
Valerie!
Valerie, open the door!
Valerie, open up!
What do you want?
Mark Tannen just
blew your alibi.
He wasn't with you
that night at the motel.
He was at the racetrack.
Yeah.
A bunch of guys and
women can vouch for him.
What?
You killed Uncle
Edwin, didn't you?
No, I was covering for Mark.
I thought Mark had killed him.
You killed Uncle Edwin!
I was at Harry's Bar
from 10:00 till 1:00.
Check with the bartender.
Do you have to do
that at the dinner table?
You don't have to look.
Well, you got the picture of
the dead body right on the bread.
Well, there.
When's the trial?
Starts tomorrow.
You must have some idea
by now who the real killer is.
Well...
It's not Valerie.
It's not her boyfriend.
How do you know? Their alibis.
It's not Drew.
Oh, sure.
It's not cute, little,
sweet, little Drew.
Well, it's not.
He stole my car.
Stealing a car is
a lot different from murder.
Well, then who's left?
Jonathan Horton.
Who's he?
He's the victim's boss.
It's him. It's got to be him.
Is it just because
you don't like him
or do you have proof?
I don't like him.
I don't have any proof.
Oh.
Hmm.
Hmm...
Seems like the
wheel of a nice car.
It is the wheel of a nice car.
All the executives in that
company drive cars like that.
Oh, nice company. Yeah.
They buy a lot of the same
model of the same car,
and then they get a
big break on the price.
You know what?
What?
Mr. Walsh's car...
is not like Mr. Horton's car.
Really?
Yeah.
Excuse me. I got to
make a phone call.
Thanks for dinner.
Great lamb. Excuse me.
If was beef stroganoff.
Hmm...
Mr. Horton,
how would you
characterize the decedent?
Was-was he
dependable, hardworking?
He was an asset
to Horton Aviation.
Extremely competent.
Loyal, fair.
Honest? To a fault.
Did you ever argue with him?
Well, we-we had some
pretty good discussions, but...
And very loudly, perhaps,
but I wouldn't say
that we... we argued.
So you had, you had discussions?
Discussions about the
military supply transport
that you'd just built?
Yes.
And the prototype alone
cost the government
nearly $1 billion, didn't it?
Yes.
Yeah, hmm, phew!
Hmm. What's it called?
The Horton MST.
It's a very complex machine.
Horton MST.
Is it expensive
because it's complex,
or because you
padded expenditures?
Like-like say for instance,
$50 instead of 50
cents for a bolt?
That's a serious
charge, Mr. Matlock...
And false.
You ordered
Mr. Walsh's files sealed
less than 24 hours
after his death. Why?
For security reasons.
Or was it because
he discovered that the
budget for the transport
had been padded?
No. Absolutely not.
I think he had, and
was collecting proof.
Mr. Walsh was a very honest man.
And he would sooner
see Horton Aviation
go down the tubes than
cheat the government.
And that is why you
were arguing with him
and why you took his files
and why you
killed him, isn't it?
This is outrageous,
insulting and false!
Lawyers, including
you, Mr. Matlock,
can be sued for defamation.
The truth is not defamation.
And the truth is, as soon as
the General Accounting Office
goes over your budget,
they will find that you
defrauded the government
to the tune of $11 million
to $12 million, won't they?
Your Honor, this
line of questioning
has nothing to
do with this case.
Goes to motive, Your Honor.
Overruled.
Thank you.
Mr. Horton, uh, all the
executives in your company
drive the same make and
model of car, don't they?
Yes. And you drove
such a car to court
today, didn't you?
Yes.
Ha. Your car.
Let's see, let's see,
let's see, let's see...
Yeah, the license plate
number is KFP848?
And you parked in the
pay parking lot space 93?
I believe so. Mm-hmm.
Would you mind if I borrowed
your keys for a few minutes?
What for?
With the court's permission...
Your car will prove who
the killer of Edwin Walsh is.
Thank you. Yeah.
You mind if the bailiff
takes a little spin?
Okay, George, back 'er right up.
Back 'er right up,
right up the side
of Mr. Walsh's car.
Okay, here, bring 'er to me.
Bring 'er to me,
bring 'er to me.
Hold!
Put 'er right there.
Good, George. Good, George.
All set, Your Honor.
Your Honor, I'd like
to repeat the objection
I raised in chambers
regarding Mr. Matlock's
dog and pony show.
So noted,
but for the moment, overruled.
Proceed, Mr. Matlock.
Now, you've already
given us your version
of what happened the night
that Mr. Walsh was murdered,
but that's not really
what happened, is it?
Of course it's what happened.
Oh, no, no, no.
You left the club, oh,
about an hour after my client.
Good night.
On your way across
the parking lot,
you passed Edwin Walsh's car.
It was empty because
he was still inside the club
auditing the books.
Then you saw Drew's car,
and inside, you saw Drew
passed out in the front seat.
Dead to the world.
And that's when it hit you.
A way of keeping Edwin Walsh
from ever blowing
the whistle on you.
First thing you did was give
Edwin Walsh's car a flat tire.
Then you got in
your car and left,
making sure you said good
night to the security guard
so that he could later testify
that you went home
before the murder.
But you didn't go home.
You parked your car on the road
by the golf course.
Got out, opened your trunk,
took out the lug wrench,
walked back to the parking lot
and waited in the shadows
for Mr. Walsh to come out.
Mr. Walsh saw the flat tire
and started to change it himself
just like you knew he would.
That's when you
hit him over the head
with the lug wrench
from your car.
A blow that killed him.
You then removed the lug
wrench from Mr. Walsh's car,
so two wrenches
wouldn't be found
at the scene of the crime.
Then you placed the
bloodstained murder weapon
in Drew's lap.
Made your way back to
your car and drove away.
How'd I do, Mr. Horton?
Not a single word
of that is true.
Then prove me wrong.
This lug wrench was
found in my client's hand.
Take it...
And remove the lug
nut from the front wheel
of Mr. Walsh's car.
Go ahead, go ahead.
That wrench doesn't seem
to want go on that nut, does it?
Well, it's probably just me.
To be honest, I've
never done this before.
Oh, oh, oh.
Well, just-just for kicks,
how about trying it on
the front wheel of your car.
Just to see.
There. Just to see.
How about that?
How about that? Perfect fit.
See, you assumed
because the cars
are the same model,
the wrenches
would be the same...
Interchangeable.
But they're not.
Because Mr. Walsh
didn't like frills.
He took the wheels that
came from the factory.
But you love frills.
You got all the frills you
could lay your hands on.
Deluxe stereo, tape deck,
special seats, remote
controlled alarm system.
Even fancy wheel covers.
See, this murder weapon
fits the wheels on your car,
because this murder
weapon came out of your trunk.
Didn't it?
We the jury find the
defendant not guilty.
Thanks. There you go.
Order, order.
As for you, Mr. Carey,
you have disrupted this
court, assaulted my bailiff
and escaped from custody.
Now while these crimes
carry jail sentences
of many long years,
in light of the time you
have spent in custody,
awaiting trial on this matter,
and the extreme emotional
tension you were under,
I am recommending
that you be sentenced
to lengthy community service.
This court is adjourned.
Mmm.
Nice bouquet.
$2.75.
A bottle?
No kidding?
We got to keep
this to ourselves.
Well, l'chaim.
Salud.
Mmm.
Well, you were
right... Drew didn't do it.
Well, I told you.
I know, but I thought
right to the last...
You told him you never had a
more contrary, cantankerous,
childish client, didn't you?
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, you got that right. Yeah.
You told him to shape up?
Oh, yeah, and quit trying
that get-rich-quick stuff.
Yeah, and settle down.
Oh, yeah, and be
the reasonable person
that his mother
raised him to be.
Well, that's the way
my mother raised me.
If she said it once, she
said it a million times:
"Lester, I want you to
be a reasonable man.
"Be strong, be firm, be tough,
"but above all...
Be reasonable. be
reasonable." Yeah.
www.tvsubtitles.net